The incredible true story of the band that defined an era.
Supersonic is a music, documentary, history film directed by Mat Whitecross.
Supersonic charts the meteoric rise of Oasis from the council estates of Manchester to
some of the biggest concerts of all time in just three short years.
This palpable, raw and moving film shines a light on one of the most genre and generation-defining British bands that has ever existed
and features candid new interviews with Noel and Liam Gallagher, their mother, and members of the band and road crew.
Self, played by Noel Gallagher.
Self, played by Liam Gallagher.
Self (as Bonehead), played by Paul Arthurs.
Self, played by Paul Gallagher.
Self, played by Peggy Gallagher.
Self, played by Tony McCarroll.
Oasis: Supersonic is a 2016 British music documentary film directed
by Mat Whitecross about the English rock band Oasis.
Asif Kapadia and James Gay-Rees, already awarded an Academy Award for the film Amy,
worked on this film respectively as executive producer and film producer.
The film was released on 26 October 2016, and was distributed in the UK by
Entertainment One and Lorton Distribution, and in the US by A24.
The film explores themes of biography, family, music.
The tone is emotional.